{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040420524","data":{"timestamp":" 947040420524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040439430","data":{"timestamp":" 947040439430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040455257","data":{"timestamp":" 947040455257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040479543","data":{"timestamp":" 947040479542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040482074","data":{"timestamp":" 947040482074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040483712","data":{"timestamp":" 947040483711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040486393","data":{"timestamp":" 947040486393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040488011","data":{"timestamp":" 947040488011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040490793","data":{"timestamp":" 947040490793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040492414","data":{"timestamp":" 947040492413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040494933","data":{"timestamp":" 947040494932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040496556","data":{"timestamp":" 947040496555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040498277","data":{"timestamp":" 947040498276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040502322","data":{"timestamp":" 947040502322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040503235","data":{"timestamp":" 947040503235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040504039","data":{"timestamp":" 947040504039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040505668","data":{"timestamp":" 947040505667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUNGULE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040508560","data":{"timestamp":" 947040508560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUNGULE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040510174","data":{"timestamp":" 947040510173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040512952","data":{"timestamp":" 947040512952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040514589","data":{"timestamp":" 947040514588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TOROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040517239","data":{"timestamp":" 947040517237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TOROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040518860","data":{"timestamp":" 947040518858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TABASAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040522034","data":{"timestamp":" 947040522033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TABASAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040523655","data":{"timestamp":" 947040523655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040526778","data":{"timestamp":" 947040526778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040528354","data":{"timestamp":" 947040528353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040531295","data":{"timestamp":" 947040531294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040533322","data":{"timestamp":" 947040533320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040533439","data":{"timestamp":" 947040533439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" 33b46600-be8e-4398-a991-ef2fadaf957a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040548053","data":{"timestamp":" 947040548052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040555122","data":{"timestamp":" 947040555122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040556751","data":{"timestamp":" 947040556750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040559790","data":{"timestamp":" 947040559790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040561415","data":{"timestamp":" 947040561414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040563959","data":{"timestamp":" 947040563959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040565570","data":{"timestamp":" 947040565569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040568104","data":{"timestamp":" 947040568103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040569713","data":{"timestamp":" 947040569712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040571476","data":{"timestamp":" 947040571475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040574145","data":{"timestamp":" 947040574145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040574750","data":{"timestamp":" 947040574750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040576370","data":{"timestamp":" 947040576369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUNGULE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040579099","data":{"timestamp":" 947040579098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUNGULE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040580681","data":{"timestamp":" 947040580681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040583392","data":{"timestamp":" 947040583391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040585020","data":{"timestamp":" 947040585020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TOROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040589085","data":{"timestamp":" 947040589084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TOROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040590718","data":{"timestamp":" 947040590717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TABASAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040596391","data":{"timestamp":" 947040596390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TABASAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_TABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040598340","data":{"timestamp":" 947040598340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TABASAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040599973","data":{"timestamp":" 947040599972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040602825","data":{"timestamp":" 947040602824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TUMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040604452","data":{"timestamp":" 947040604451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040606926","data":{"timestamp":" 947040606926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040608956","data":{"timestamp":" 947040608954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040609064","data":{"timestamp":" 947040609064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" b2de0695-681d-45d9-b816-e695cb62082b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TRENI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040633161","data":{"timestamp":" 947040633161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_O-N-T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040636695","data":{"timestamp":" 947040636695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_CH-L-T"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040640049","data":{"timestamp":" 947040640048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-V-T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040643352","data":{"timestamp":" 947040643352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_S-P-T"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040646987","data":{"timestamp":" 947040646986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-R-W"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040650512","data":{"timestamp":" 947040650511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-W"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040653978","data":{"timestamp":" 947040653978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-U"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040657988","data":{"timestamp":" 947040657988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-V-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040661742","data":{"timestamp":" 947040661742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-K-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040666255","data":{"timestamp":" 947040666255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-G-A"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040672016","data":{"timestamp":" 947040672014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" f5e2c709-3b92-4895-bbe5-e1ea2b515bdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-G-A"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040712359","data":{"timestamp":" 947040712359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_CH_T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040719007","data":{"timestamp":" 947040719007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_T_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040725689","data":{"timestamp":" 947040725689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_R_T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040732363","data":{"timestamp":" 947040732362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_T_H"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040739034","data":{"timestamp":" 947040739034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_T_A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040745692","data":{"timestamp":" 947040745692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_O_CH"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040752327","data":{"timestamp":" 947040752324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_L_T"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040758975","data":{"timestamp":" 947040758974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_V_S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040765607","data":{"timestamp":" 947040765606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_H_N"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040772254","data":{"timestamp":" 947040772254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_T_S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040784308","data":{"timestamp":" 947040784307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054647"," gameId":" c6267be5-dfc4-48dd-aa34-d2e473ebd1d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_G_T_S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}